Guide to the George P. Garrett Papers, 1929-2008 (bulk 1960-2000)
George P. Garrett papers 1929-2008 (bulk 1960-2000)
- Correspondence Series, 1929-1995 and undated
  - Alphabetical Correspondence Subseries: Group A, ca. 1961-1995 and undated
    Contains letters from students, colleagues, friends, literary figures, and family members concerning literary, academic, and personal matters. Arranged alphabetically by the last name of the correspondent. All items from each correspondent are contained within one folder unless otherwise indicated.
    - Aaron, Howard (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Abbot, Louise
    - Abdou, Elias
    - Abse, Dannie
    - Ackerman, Diane
    - Addison, Lee
    - Ager, Verkuilen
    - Akerman, Hugh
    - Akerman, Robert
    - Albright, William (Bill)
    - Albritton, A. Dallas
    - Aldershof, Mrs. Kent
    - Allen, Bruce
    - Allen, Eloise
    - Allen, John A.
    - Allen, Mrs.R (Frani)
    - Anderson, Leif
    - Anderson, Emily Draper
    - Antrim, Don
    - Antrim, Harry
    - Appleman, Philip
    - Ardizzone, Tony
    - Armstrong, Robert G.
    - Arnold, Judd
    - Ashbery, John
    - Ashley, Franklin
    - Atkins, Mary Ellen
    - Atkins, Tom
    - Atkins, Thomas
    - Atkinson, Clinton J.
    - Aycock, Wendell
    - A (Misc.)
    - Babcock, Bert
    - Bagg, Robert
    - Bain, Robert
    - Baird, Ida
    - Baird, Max
    - Baker, Carlos
    - Bale, Joy
    - Ball, Donald
    - Barnstone, H.
    - Barnstone, Willis
    - Barrett, James Lee
    - Barrett, Marvin
    - Barriom Raymond
    - Barrol, J. Leeds
    - Barry, Richard A.
    - Barth, John
    - Battestin, Martin and Ruth
    - Baumbach (see Bumas)
    - Baumbach, Jonathan
    - Bausch, Richard
    - Bayle, Joy
    - Beachman, Walton
    - Beattie, Ann
    - Beck, Virginia L.
    - Beebe, Anne
    - Bell, Charles G.
    - Bell, Madison
    - Bell, Marvin
    - Belitt, Ben
    - Benedetti, Robert L.
    - Benedict, Pinckney
    - Berlind, Bruce
    - Bernhard, Ruth
    - Bernstein, Jane
    - Berry, D. C.
    - Berry, Jason
    - Berto, Giuseppe
    - Bertolino, James
    - Berryhill, Michael
    - Betts, Doris
    - Blotner, Joseph
    - Biddle, Katherine (Mrs. Francis)
    - Biquenet, John
    - Bitker, Marjorie
    - Bjornson, Richard
    - Blackburn, William
    - Blackmur, R.P.
    - Blotner, J.L.
    - Boatwright, James
    - Bode, Carl
    - Bogan, Louise
    - Bonazzi, Bob
    - Booth, Jay
    - Borden, Ed. B.
    - Bornhauser, Fred
    - Bourjaily, Vance
    - Bowers, Fredson
    - Boyle, Kay
    - Bracker, Jon
    - Bradley, Jerry ( The New Mexico Humanities Review)
    - Briggs, Curtisy
    - Brinni, John Maliom
    - Brock, Van
    - Brookes, Jacqueline
    - Brooks, Cleanth
    - Brooks, Roger
    - Broughton, Irv
    - Brower, Brock
    - Brown, Gwyneth
    - Brown, Jerry
    - Brown, Pryde
    - Brown, Vaughan
    - Bruccoli, Matthew
    - Buechner, Frederick
    - Bumas, Jonathan
    - Burkert, Claire
    - Burroughs, Edgar Rice
    - Bush, G. F.
    - Byron, Stuart
    - B (Misc.)
    - Cacciatore, Edoardo
    - Caetani, Princess
    - Cain, Gloria
    - Cajina-Vega, Mario
    - Campbell, John
    - Campo, Cristina
    - Cane, Priscilla
    - Caples, Minerva
    - Cardwell, Harry
    - Carr, Barnes
    - Carr, John, (5 folders) (Box Alpha. Corr. A2)
    - Carringer, Robert
    - Carter, Virginia
    - Case, William
    - Cassill, Kay
    - Cassill, R. V.
    - Chappell, Fred
    - Chappell, Patsy
    - Chenoweth, H. Avery
    - Cherry, Kelly
    - Cheuse, Alan
    - Cheever, John
    - Chilton, W. E.
    - Christ, Ronald
    - Chute, Carolyn
    - Ciardi, John
    - Clark, David R.
    - Clark, Geoff
    - Clemmons, Walter
    - Clift, Gary
    - Cogshell, Rosanne
    - Cohen, Marc
    - Cohen, Sarah B.
    - Coindreau, Maurice
    - Coleman, M. M.
    - Collin, Francis
    - Collmer, Robert G.
    - Colony, Joyce
    - Colum, Padrick (Padraic?)
    - Colvert, Jim
    - Commins, Dorothy
    - Conner, Jack E.
    - Cook, Thomas
    - Cooley, Peter
    - Copper, Harriet
    - Core, George
    - Corn, Charles
    - Corrigan, Robert W.
    - Corrington, John William
    - Corrington, William
    - Cousin, Herbert
    - Cowen, Walker
    - Cowley, Malcolm
    - Cox, Nana
    - Cox, Steve
    - Coxe, Louis O.
    - Creagh, John P.
    - Creeger, George
    - Crepeau, Marcel G.
    - Crow, Edith (Baker)
    - Currier, John
    - C (Misc.)
    - Dahl, Roald
    - Danielson, Patricia, (3 folders)
    - Danielson, Patricia, (2 folders) (Box Alpha. Corr. A3)
    - Daniell, Rosemary
    - Darr, Ann, (2 folders)
    - Davis, Paxton
    - Davis, L.J.
    - Day, Douglas
    - Day, Robert
    - Degener, Claire
    - DeJong, David C.
    - Delbanco, Nicholas
    - Den Boer, James
    - Denham, Robert
    - Denny, Dave
    - Denny, Reuel
    - Denton, Mrs. Walter (Virginia)
    - Dern, Susan
    - Dew, Joan
    - Deutsche, Babette
    - Diamond, I. A. L.
    - Dick, Donna
    - Dickey, James
    - Dickey, R. P.
    - Dickey, Larry
    - Dike, Donald
    - Dillard, Annie
    - Dillard, Richard, (2 folders)
    - Dinsmore, Brad
    - Dipiero, Simione
    - Di Piero, W. S.
    - Doar, Harriet
    - Dodrill, Davan
    - Domroe, Elissa
    - Donadio, Candida
    - Dorris, George
    - Dow, Paul E.
    - Dowden, Will
    - Downer, Alan
    - Downs, Robert C.S.
    - Drinkwater, Harry
    - Dunlap, Bernie
    - Dunn, Alice and Evans
    - Dunning, Steve
    - Durbin, Reed
    - Dutcher, Lavalle Simms
    - Duvall, Severn
    - Dabney -- Dzul
    - Early, Benjamin
    - Early, Robert
    - East, Charles
    - Eastlake, William
    - Easton, Richard, (2 folders)
    - Eaton, Charles Edward
    - Eckstrom, Christine
    - Eddins, Dwight
    - Edwards, Emily B.
    - Edwards, Junius
    - Edwards, Rena
    - Ehrenpreis, Irwin
    - Eisiminger, Skip
    - Elliott, George P., (2 folders)
    - Elliott, Lee
    - Ellis, Herbert
    - Ellison, Harlan
    - Ellison, Ralph, (2 folders)
    - Elman, Richard, (2 folders)
    - Elwood, W. A.
    - Elzinga, Jeff
    - Emerson, O.B.
    - Emerson, William
    - Emery, Jim
    - Emory, Emma Gray
    - Engel, Monroe
    - Engleby, Janeen
    - Engels, John
    - Englert, Hedy
    - Epps, A. C.
    - Epps, A.C. (Mrs.)
    - Epps, Garrett
    - Epps, John
    - Epps, Kay
    - Epps, Roseanne
    - Epstein, Leslie
    - Epstein, Seymour
    - Erwin, Anne
    - Estrater, Mary Peterson
    - Evans, Patrick
    - Evans, Robert
    - Evans, Timothy
    - Evatt, H. Parker
    - Ewell, Nat
    - Eyster, Warren
    - Fales, Angela B.
    - Faner, Robert
    - Farris, Jack
    - Faulk, Carolyn
    - Favazza, Armando
    - Fensterman, R.J.
    - Fentine, Nancy
    - Fialkowski, Barbara
    - Fiedler, Leslie
    - Finkel, Don
    - Finks, Richard
    - Fisher, John G. (Jack)
    - Fitts, Dudley
    - Flagg, Fannie
    - Flatow, Gail
    - Flavin, Jack
    - Flowerday, Charlie
    - Flynt, Candace
    - Fokes, Loretta S. (Box Alpha. Corr. A4)
    - Foote, Bud
    - Foote, Shelby
    - Forche, Carolyn
    - Ford, Jesse Hill, (2 folders)
    - Ford, Michael
    - Ford, Richard
    - Foulke, Robert (Bud)
    - Fowler, Albert
    - Fowles, John
    - Frankel, Phyllis
    - Franks, Zarito
    - Fraser, Russell A., (2 folders)
    - Frazier, Allie
    - Fredericks, Claude
    - Frederickson, Ronald
    - Friend, Peter
    - Friedman, Robert
    - Frumkin, Gene
    - Fussell, Betty
    - Fussell, Paul
    - Gadeloff, Alice
    - Gagliano, Frank
    - Galler, David
    - Gallopoulous, Greg
    - Galvin, Brendan, (3 folders)
    - Galvin, Peter
    - Ganz, Earl
    - Gardner, Jim
    - Gardner, John
    - Gardner, Stephen
    - Garey, R. J.
    - Garrett, Alice
    - Garrett, Alexandra (Sandy)
    - Garrett, Bill
    - Garret, Aunt Dot and Uncle Dave
    - Garrett, George III
    - Garrett, Helen
    - Garrett, Peter
    - Garrett, Rosalie
    - Garrett, Mrs. George (Susan), (2 folders)
    - Garrett, W. M.
    - Garrison, Christian
    - Garrison, Silas H.
    - Gary, Hattie
    - Gautreaux, Tim
    - Gelfman, Jane
    - Gelfant, Blanche
    - Genman, Meghan
    - Gery, John
    - Ghiselin, Brewster
    - Ghislen, Campbell
    - Gibbons, Reginald
    - Gibson, Margaret
    - Gilchrist, Ellen
    - Gillespie, George
    - Gioia, Dana
    - Girault, Norton
    - Glass, Malcolm
    - Glenn, Vernon
    - Glickman, Constance
    - Godfrey, Kathleen
    - Goertz, Don
    - Goff, Paula
    - Goff, Ted
    - Goheen, Bob
    - Gold, Herbert
    - Goldman, William
    - Goldwyn, Samuel, Jr.
    - Goodall, H. Lloyd
    - Goodman, Rita
    - Goodwin, Steve
    - Gordon, Thomas
    - Gowland, Peter
    - Goyen, William
    - Graaf, Homer J.
    - Gragg, Rod
    - Graham, Burke
    - Graham, Christine
    - Graham, Courtenay
    - Graham, John
    - Graves, John
    - Green, Samuel
    - Greer, Ben
    - Gregory, Mike
    - Greiner, Don
    - Grey, Robert
    - Greyson, Richard
    - Griffith, Wm. (Bill)
    - Groves, Gerald
    - Guerard, Albert J.
    - Gunter, Brad
    - Guerra, Wendy
    - Gwynn, Sam
    - G. (Misc.)
    - Haferd, Maggie (Box Alpha. Corr. A5)
    - Hagstrom, Jack
    - Hagy, Alyson
    - Hall, Donald
    - Hall, Tim
    - Hammer, Jeanne-Ruth
    - Hammond, J. E., (2 folders)
    - Hammond, Karla
    - Hankla, Cathy
    - Hankla, Susan
    - Hannah, Barry
    - Hanrahan, Jack and Joyce
    - Hardison, O. B., (2 folders)
    - Hardy, Bill
    - Harper, George M.
    - Harper, Michael S.
    - Harrington, Donna
    - Harrington, Evans
    - Harris, Allen
    - Harris, Marina (Littig)
    - Harris, Melanie
    - Harrison, Stanley
    - Harrison, William
    - Hart, Barbara J.
    - Harvard, John
    - Harvey, Evelyn
    - Haskins, Sam and Alida
    - Hassan, Ihab
    - Havard, William C.
    - Hawkes, John
    - Hawkins, Sherman
    - Hawkins, Tom
    - Hazel, Robert
    - Hazo, Samuel
    - Hebert, Annabelle
    - Heblich, Fred
    - Heller, Betty, (2 folders)
    - Hemley, Elaine Gottlieb
    - Hendel, Richard
    - Henderson, Archibald
    - Hendrie, Don
    - Henry, Dewitt, (2 folders)
    - Hereford, Frank L.
    - Herman, Stephen J.
    - Herrmann, John
    - Herzig, Jack
    - Hewitt, Geof
    - Hilliard, Richard
    - Hirsch, Don
    - Hiwck, Jon
    - Hobby, Diana Poteat
    - Hodges, Harriet
    - Hoffman, Daniel, (2 folders)
    - Hogg, Brian D.
    - Holinger, William, (2 folders)
    - Holland, Gill
    - Hollander, Robert
    - Holmberg, Lonnie
    - Holmes, Theodore
    - Hood, Mary
    - Hooker, Michael
    - Hope, Winston (Rev.)
    - Hopen, Stuart
    - Houston, Bob
    - Howarth, Bill
    - Howes, Barbara
    - Hubler, Ted
    - Huddle, David, (2 folders)
    - Hudgins, Andrew
    - Hudson, Rebecca
    - Huelster, Joy
    - Huey, Tommy
    - Huff, Robert
    - Hughes, Bonnie
    - Hugo, Richard
    - Humphries, Rolfe
    - Hunt, Ben
    - Hunting, Constance
    - H (Misc.)
    - Ibranyi-Kiss, Siddigi
    - Igo, John
    - Inabinett, E.L.
    - Irwin, Anne
    - Isaacs, Neal
    - Israel, Charles
    - Ivanhoe, Faye
    - Iverson, Mary
    - Jackson, Elliele
    - Jackson, John
    - Jacobs, Lucky
    - Jacobson, Jane
    - Jacobson, Josephine (Box Alpha. Corr. A6)
    - James, Stuart
    - Janeck, Don
    - Janiszewski, Steve
    - Janowitz, Phyllis
    - Janowitz, Tama (Tom A.)
    - Jaro, Benita
    - Jeffrey, Susu
    - Jenkins, David
    - Jenkins, Don
    - Jenkins, Lyll Becerra
    - Jeter, Jim and Marian
    - John, Dorothy
    - Johnson, Alan
    - Johnson, B.S.
    - Johnson, Carl (Capt.)
    - Johnson, E.D.H.
    - Johnson, Gayle
    - Johnson, Mary Ann
    - Johnson, Larry
    - Johnson, Norah
    - Johnston, Dan/Pam
    - Johnston, Tom
    - Jones, Edward P.
    - Jones, Lawrence Wm.
    - Jones, Ray
    - Jones, Thomas F.
    - Jong-van Leer, Dola
    - Josephy, Jennifer
    - Joyce, William
    - Joynes, St. Leger (Monty)
    - Juergeuse, Hanes
    - Jupp, Francine
    - Jupp, Garrett
    - Justice, Donald
    - Jackson -- Jones
    - Kafka, Kimberly
    - Kaplan, Bernie
    - Karchmer, Sylvan
    - Katona, Anna
    - Katzenbach, Maria
    - Kearney, Lawrence
    - Keeble, John
    - Keeley, Edmund (Mike)
    - Keeley, R.V.
    - Keens, Bill
    - Kehl, D.G.
    - Kellogg, Robert
    - Kemp, Elizabeth
    - Kendrick, Stephen
    - Keni
    - Kennedy, X.J.
    - Kessler, Edward, (2 folders)
    - Kessler, Milton
    - Kestner, Joe
    - Kestner, Sue
    - Kibler, Jim
    - Kimball, Philip, (2 folders)
    - Kimber, R.B.
    - Kimble, Cary
    - Kherdian, David
    - Kinnell, Galway
    - King, Edward
    - King, Helen
    - King, Kevin
    - Kinnear, Cal
    - Kirby-Smith, Tom
    - Kirkwood, Richard E.
    - Kirsch, Arthur
    - Kittrell, Robert
    - Kizer, Carolyn
    - Klappert, Peter
    - Knapp, John
    - Knapp, Ruth, (5 folders)
    - Knies, Liz
    - Knott, John R.
    - Koepenick, Martin
    - Koethe, John L.
    - Kohler, Dayton
    - Kostelanetz, Richard, (2 folders)
    - Krasney, Martin
    - Kray, Elizabeth
    - Kruchkow, Diane
    - Kumin, Maxine
    - Kurtz, John
    - Kahanna -- Kyle
    - Lacey, Robert
    - Laing, Alexander
    - Lakehomez, Leona
    - Lampton, Nana
    - Lander, Paul
    - Landis, Jim
    - Landis, Jamey
    - Landsberg, Melvin
    - Longbaum, Robert
    - LaRiche, William
    - Larry, Richard G.
    - LaSalle, Peter, (2 folders)
    - Lawder, Alan
    - Lawder, Doug
    - Lawler, Donald L.
    - Lawson, Anna Logan
    - Lazard, Naomi
    - LeCouras, Pete
    - Lee, Sara
    - Leggett, John
    - Legler, Phil
    - Lehman, David (Box Alpha. Corr. A7)
    - Leindecker, Gloria
    - Leland, H. Cheves
    - Leland, John G.
    - Lelchuk, Alan
    - Levine, Paul
    - Leviten, David
    - Lewis, J.A. (Jim)
    - Lewis, Jean
    - Liang, Alexander
    - Lieber, Marjorie
    - Lindell, Richard L.
    - Linden, Ed
    - Linthicum, John
    - Lipinsky, Mike
    - Lippman, Stan
    - Lisca, Peter
    - Lish, Gordon
    - Little, John
    - Lloyd, Thomas
    - Lobrano, Dorothy
    - Loch, Anita C.
    - Logan, Ann
    - Logan, Bill
    - Lolos, Kimon
    - Longley, John
    - López, Minerva G.
    - Lord, Gigi
    - Loughran, Joe
    - Love, James A.
    - Love, Spencie
    - Lovelace, Jon
    - Lubenkov, Paul
    - Luce, Greg
    - Lucid, Bob
    - Ludwig, R.M.
    - Lueders, Ed
    - Lumpkin, Arthur
    - Luschei, Glenna
    - Lyons, Gene
    - Lasser -- Lynch
    - Macauley, Robie, (2 folders)
    - Maclay, Joanna
    - Maclehose, Christopher
    - MacShane, Frank
    - Madden, David
    - Magill, Frank
    - Maiolo, Joseph
    - Maiolo, Mike
    - Malamud, Bernard
    - Malinowitz, Michael
    - Manchester, William
    - Mann, Jim (James)
    - Manning, Steve
    - Marcus, Alan
    - Margolis, John D.
    - Marin, Dan
    - Massey, David
    - Massey, Linton
    - Masters, Hillary
    - Mathews, Harry
    - Mathis, Cleopatra
    - Matthews, Jack
    - Maxson, Harry
    - May, James
    - McAdams, Bill
    - McAfee, Tom
    - McAuley, James
    - McCaffree, Robert
    - McCann, Richard J.
    - McClellan, Anita D.
    - McClellan, Betsy
    - McClelland, Alice
    - McClelland, Craig
    - McCloskey, Mark
    - McCrindle, J.F.
    - McCullough, Frank
    - McConkey, James
    - McCorkle, Jill
    - McCrindle, J.F.
    - McDougall, Jo
    - McFee, John
    - McGonigle, Thomas, (2 folders)
    - McGuire, J.E.F.
    - McHale, Tom
    - McHaney, Tom
    - McHugh, Heather
    - McKay, Blythe
    - McMillen, Sheila
    - McMurtry, Larry
    - McNally, James
    - Meacham, Harry
    - Meador Daniel J.
    - Mearstler, Helen
    - Medina, Harold
    - Meinke, Peter
    - Meisel, Martin C.
    - Meredith, William
    - Meriwether, J.B.
    - Meriwether, Jim
    - Merritt, Travis
    - Metz, Brian
    - Metz, Jerred
    - Metz, Robin
    - Mewshaw, Michael
    - Milks, Betsy
    - Miller, Heather Ross
    - Miller, J.P.
    - Miller, Vassar
    - Milligan, Tom
    - Millman, Larry
    - Millon, Henry (Box Alpha. Corr. A8)
    - Milstein, Stuart
    - Minton, Helena
    - Mirsky, Mark Jay
    - Mitgang, Herbert
    - Moffatt, James V.
    - Moffett, Judy
    - Montgomery, Marion, (2 folders)
    - Moody, Ché
    - Mooney, Jack
    - Moore, Bryan
    - Moore, Brian
    - Moore, Hal
    - Moore, Marianne
    - Moore, Richard
    - Morgan, Robert
    - Morrin, George
    - Morris, Robert L.
    - Morris, Willie
    - Morris, Wright
    - Morrison, William W.
    - Morrow, Mark
    - Morse, Samuel French
    - Moscoso, Pete
    - Mosher, Harold
    - Moss, Howard
    - Mott, Michael
    - Mueller, Craig
    - Munck, Ann
    - Murphy, Richard
    - Murray, Bill
    - M (Misc.), (2 folders)
    - Nadelson, Reggie
    - Nail, Leslie
    - Napier, Gus
    - Naponick, John
    - Nash, Edith
    - Nash, H.C.
    - Naslund, Sena
    - Nassar, Gene
    - Nathans, Rhoda
    - Natoli, Joseph
    - Neiman, Fraser
    - Neiseman, Jack
    - Nelson, Howie
    - Nelson, Margaret A.
    - Nelson, Kent
    - Nelson, R. Fredrik
    - Nes, Eliot
    - Nemerov, Howard
    - Neuffer, Claude
    - Neway, Patricia
    - Newman, Frank
    - Newman, Paul Baker
    - Nicholson, Somerville
    - Nichols, Stephen G.
    - Nicoletta, Peter
    - Niles, Mrs. John J.
    - Nims, John F., (2 folders)
    - Nin, Anais
    - Nixon, Richard
    - Nohle, Ann
    - Nolan, Tom
    - Noll, Bink, (2 folders)
    - Norfleet, Elizabeth
    - Norris, Leslie
    - Norse, Harold
    - Northouse, Cam
    - Norton, Sidney
    - Nyberg, Ben
    - Oberdorfer, Don
    - O'Brien, Frank
    - O'Connor, Mary
    - O'Connor, Philip, (2 folders)
    - O'Cridain, Sean
    - O'Donnell, Patrick
    - O'Gorman, Ned
    - O'Grady, Desmond
    - O'Hara, John
    - Olivar, Madire
    - Olson, Charles
    - Olsen, David
    - Olsen, Eric
    - Olson, Paul
    - Olsen, Tillie
    - Omwake, John
    - O'Neill, Joanna
    - O'Neill, Kevin
    - Osborn, Carolyn
    - Overall, William
    - Owen, Guy (2)
    - Owens, Sue
    - Packard, William
    - PacPerson, Bettijane
    - Paine, Lewis
    - Palmer, Bryan
    - Parish, Mike
    - Parker, Boyce Lee
    - Parker, Lois M.
    - Parker, Wyman
    - Pasco, Cauny
    - Paton, Jack, (2 folders)
    - Pawlowski, Robert
    - Payne, Betsy P.
    - Payne, Ginnie
    - Peck, Dick
    - Peck, John
    - Peden, William, (2 folders)
    - Peet, Mary Ann
    - Pelletier, Gaston
    - Penick, Douglas
    - Pennybacker, Ruth
    - Percival, Percy
    - Pesta, John
    - Peterson, Mary
    - Peterson, Jim
    - Pettis, Maggie
    - Pettit, Molly
    - Pevear, Richard
    - Philbrick, Johanne
    - Philips, Jim
    - Piercy, Marge
    - Pitchford, Kenneth
    - Platt, Eugene
    - Plumly, Hope (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Plumly, Stanley
    - Poliakoff, Cindy
    - Pollard, Joyce
    - Pomeroy, Ralph
    - Ponder, Dulane
    - Ponder, Leanne
    - Porter, Mrs. Arabel. J.
    - Porter, Norman
    - Porterfield, Robert
    - Portis, Rowe, (2 folders)
    - Posner, David
    - Poster, Carol, (3 folders)
    - Powers, Pamela
    - Powell, Robert
    - Prager, Robert
    - Preston, Daniel
    - Price, Phyllis
    - Price, Reynolds
    - Pruden, Mrs. Roy D.
    - Prunty, Wyatt
    - Purviance, Donald
    - Palmer -- Puteo
    - Quasimodo, Salvatore
    - Quigley, Austin
    - Ragan, Sam
    - Raiziss, Sonia
    - Ramsey, Paul, (2 folders)
    - Ramsey, Robert
    - Randall, Julia, (2 folders)
    - Ransom, John Crowe
    - Rappold, Robert
    - Rath, Roger
    - Ratliff, V.K.
    - Ravetch, Irving
    - Ravenel, Shannon
    - Ray, David
    - Ray, George
    - Real, Jere
    - Reddick, Pat and Tom
    - Reed, Kit, (2 folders)
    - Reed, Mark
    - Rees, Ennis
    - Reich, Dave
    - Reiter, Tom
    - Remis, Ralph
    - Renner, Bruce
    - Reynolds, Cedric S.
    - Reynolds, Max
    - Rhodes, Byno
    - Rhodes, Richard
    - Ricci, Julio
    - Ritter, Lucy C.
    - Ritalin, Thane
    - Roberts, Laurence
    - Robbins, Martin
    - Robinson, Ann
    - Robinson, Bill
    - Rodenbeck, John
    - Roe, Connie
    - Roetzel, Larry
    - Rogers, Viola
    - Rollinson, Phil
    - Rooke, Leon
    - Root, William Pitt, (2 folders)
    - Root, Judith
    - Roper, Mrs. George C.
    - Rose, Charles
    - Roseliep, Raymond, (2 folders)
    - Rosen, Kenneth, (2 folders)
    - Rosenbaum, Robert
    - Rosenfeld, Irene
    - Rospigliosi, Princess Margherita
    - Ross, Dan
    - Ross, David
    - Ross, Jean
    - Rossberg, Stephen
    - Roth, George L.
    - Roth, Philip
    - Rovit, Earl (Bud)
    - Ruark, Gib, (2 folders)
    - Rubin, David
    - Rubin, Larry, (2 folders)
    - Rubin, Louis, (2 folders)
    - Ruffin, Paul
    - Rudnicki, Larry
    - Ruefle, Mary
    - Ruffin, Paul
    - Rulon-Miller, Elizabeth
    - Ryan, Rick
    - Rybaker, Lucille
    - R (Misc.)
    - Sadoff, Ira
    - Saltz, Bob
    - Sanchez, Sonia
    - Sanders, Scott
    - Sandnes, Don
    - Sandy, Stephen
    - Sapperstein, Michael
    - Sarton, May
    - Savage, Catherine
    - Schaible, Robert
    - Schelling, Mrs. H.M.
    - Schevill, James
    - Schoenberger, Nancy
    - Schohart, Art
    - Scholes, Robert
    - Schönholzer, Annemarie
    - Schultz, John
    - Schulz, Gretchen
    - Schutt, Christine
    - Scott, Carolynne
    - Scott, Nathan
    - Scott, Susan R.
    - Sears, Cathy
    - Sears, Stan
    - Seay, James (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Secrest, Mrs. Meryle
    - Seebring, Tom
    - Segal, Lore
    - Semmler, Mrs. R. A.
    - Semsibar, Judith
    - Seper, Warren
    - Settle, Mary Lee
    - Seward, William, (2 folders)
    - Shackleford, Rudy
    - Shaffer, Stephen Mayo
    - Shannon, Edgar
    - Shapard, Robert
    - Sharp, Rhod
    - Sharpless, F. Parvin
    - Sharpless, Geoff
    - Sheldon, Tim
    - Shelton, Lois
    - Shelnutt, Eve
    - Sheppard, Patricia
    - Shereff, Dorothy
    - Sherwood, Dolly
    - Short, Carvel G.
    - Short, James
    - Shugrue, Michael
    - Shumway, Mary
    - Sibley, Fred
    - Siegel, Robert
    - Silver, Kelly
    - Simms, Peg
    - Simmons, J. Edgar
    - Simon, John
    - Simon, Rose
    - Simpson, John
    - Simpson, Louis
    - Simpson, Michael
    - Sinclair, Bennie Lee
    - Singer, Ron
    - Skinnner, Knute
    - Sklarew, Myra
    - Slavitt, David, (8 folders)
    - Slavitt, Lynn
    - Slocum, Meg
    - Smith, Barry
    - Smith, Ben
    - Smith, Bob
    - Smith, Dave
    - Smith, Ed
    - Smith, Gerda
    - Smith, Glenn
    - Smith, Lee
    - Smith, Stephen E.
    - Smith, William Jay
    - Snipes, Wilson
    - Snodgrass, W.D.
    - Snow, Wilbert
    - Sopko, Jack
    - Sobehack, Tom
    - Sorel, Julian
    - Sorenson, Dale
    - Sorrells, Helen
    - Sorrells, Bob
    - Southall, Deire
    - Spackman, Peter
    - Spacks, Barry
    - Sparks, Larry
    - Spears, Monroe K.
    - Spier, Jacquelyn
    - Spingarn, Lawrence
    - Spireng, Matthew
    - Squires, Radcliffe
    - Staley, Eric
    - Standiford, Les
    - Stanford, Frank
    - Standley, Fred
    - Stanton, Maura
    - Starbuck, George (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Steedman, C. Richard
    - Steele, Max
    - Steele, Paul
    - Stegner, Wallace
    - Stein, Edward
    - Steinke, Darcey
    - Stephens, Martha
    - Stern, Dan
    - Stevens, Holly, (2 folders)
    - Stevenson, John W.
    - Stillwell, John
    - Starr, Bill
    - Stocker, Arthur
    - Stokes, Michael A.
    - Stokesbury, Leon
    - Stone, Ed
    - Stone, John
    - Stone, Nancy
    - Stone, Naomi
    - Stone, Ruth
    - Stott, Michael J.
    - Stout, Rex
    - Stovall, Floyd
    - Strachan, Bill
    - Strand, Mark
    - Strater, Mary P.
    - Stuart, Dabney
    - Stuit, Dewey
    - Styron, William
    - Sullivan, Chester
    - Sullivan, Nancy
    - Sullivan, Peggy
    - Sullivan, Walter
    - Summers, Hollis
    - Sverdling, Alex
    - Swan, Gladys
    - Swann, Brian
    - Swann, Roberta
    - Sward, Robert
    - Swiggart, Peter
    - Symons, Julian
    - Szathmary, Arthur
    - Szogy, Alex
    - Santos-Steinman
    - Tagliabue, John
    - Tambimuttu
    - Tannen, Robert
    - Tanner, Douglas